millsandboon.co.uk 2016-10-12

# Romance, fiction books and ebooks from Mills & Boon

HarperCollins Publishers Ltd and www.millsandboon.co.uk are totally committed to the very highest level of customer service and this includes protecting your privacy and treating your personal information with the utmost confidentiality. We use the information we collect about you to process orders and to provide an individual and personalised experience and shopping area for you at www.millsandboon.co.uk.

## Information we collect and why?

\- Each order you make with us requires that you provide us with your name, e-mail address, delivery address, credit or debit card number and the card's expiry date. This permits us to process and fulfil your orders and to notify you of the status of your order.

\- We also ask for your telephone number which enables us to contact you urgently if there are any problems with your order.

\- When you enter a contest or other promotional feature, we may ask for your name, address and e-mail address so we can administer the contest and notify winners.

\- We personalise your shopping service by using your purchases to shape our recommendations about other books that might be of interest to you.

\- We also monitor customer traffic patterns and site usage to help us develop the design and layout of our site.

\- We may also use the information we collect to occasionally notify you about important functionality changes to the Web site, new services and special offers that we think you'll find useful.

\- We may also approach you (ourselves or via a third party) to ask you questions to help us improve our websites and the goods and services we offer e.g. by asking you to participate in a survey about topical issues conducted by us or trusted partners or third parties. We will always let you know before you participate in any survey how any information you provide will be used.

If you would rather not receive this information, please send an e-mail to [csmillsandboon@harpercollins.co.uk](mailto:%20csmillsandboon@harpercollins.co.uk)

## What do we do to protect your information?

When you place orders or access your account information, we offer the use of a secure server. The secure server software (SSL) encrypts all information you input before it is sent to us. Furthermore, as required by the UK Data Protection Acts of 1984 and 1998, we follow strict security procedures in the storage and disclosure of information which you have given us, to prevent unauthorised access. Our security procedures mean that we may occasionally request proof of identity before we are able to disclose sensitive information to you.

## Apart from being sweet treats, what do you need to know about "cookies"?

Cookies are small pieces of information that are stored by your browser on your computer's hard drive. Our cookies do not contain any personally identifying information, but they do enable us to relate your use of our site to information that you have specifically and knowingly provided to us.

Most browsers automatically accept cookies, but you can usually change your browser to prevent that. Even without a cookie, you can still use most of the features on our site, including placing items in your shopping basket and purchasing them.

**Opt in / Opt out**

As a customer of Mills & Boon, you can receive our free email messages and get exclusive, tailored product offers and deals based on your preferences, browsing behaviour and the purchases you make from Mills & Boon.

If you do not wish to receive these emails you have the option to opt out at any time by clicking on the unsubscribe link found at the bottom of our emails and/or send an e-mail message to [csmillsandboon@harpercollins.co.uk](mailto:%20csmillsandboon@harpercollins.co.uk) to change your preferences. Remember to change your preferences for each of the e-mail accounts you have given us.

## Will we disclose the information we collect to outside parties?

www.millsandboon.co.uk may choose to sell, trade or rent your personal information to trustworthy third parties, but should you wish us not to do so then send an e-mail message to [csmillsandboon@harpercollins.co.uk](mailto:%20csmillsandboon@harpercollins.co.uk). (If you use more than one e-mail address to access us, send this message from each e-mail account you use.) Also, we may provide aggregate statistics about our customers, sales, traffic patterns and related site information to reputable third-party vendors, but these statistics will not include any personal identifying information.

The data that we collect from you may be transferred to, and stored on, servers in a country outside the European Economic Area ("EEA"). It may also be processed by staff operating outside the EEA who work for us or for one of our suppliers. Such staff maybe engaged in, among other things, maintaining our sites, the fulfilment of your order, the processing of your payment details and the provision of support services. By submitting your personal data, you agree to this transfer, storing or processing. We will take all steps reasonably necessary to ensure that your data is treated securely and in accordance with this privacy policy. All information you provide to us is stored on secure servers. Any payment transactions will be encrypted using SSL technology. Where we have given you (or where you have chosen) a password which enables you to access certain parts of our site, you are responsible for keeping this password confidential. We ask you not to share a password with anyone. Unfortunately, the transmission of information via the internet is not completely secure. Although we will do our best to protect your personal data, we cannot guarantee the security of your data transmitted to our site; any transmission is at your own risk. Once we have received your information, we will use strict procedures and security features to try to prevent unauthorised access. We may also share your data with third-parties who are providing us with services to help with our business operations and provide the websites to you. Where a lawful request is made to us we also reserve the right to access and disclose your personal information to governments, law enforcement agencies or other parties whose request we reasonably consider to be justified to comply with any law.

## In Summary

We are committed to protecting your privacy. We use the information we collect on the site to make your time and interest inwww.millsandboon.co.uk possible and to enhance your overall experience at www.millsandboon.co.uk.

## Your Consent

By using our site, you consent to the collection and use of this information by www.millsandboon.co.uk. If we decide to make any changes to this privacy policy, we will post those changes on this page so that you are always aware of what information we collect, how we use it and under what circumstances we disclose it.

## Our Company Details:

Harper Collins Publishers Ltd

Registered office:

Westerhill Road

Bishopbriggs

Glasgow

G64 2QT

Registered Number: SC027389

Phone:

Non-UK residents: +44 844 844 1351  
UK residents only: 0844 844 1351

ROI: 01 278 2062
